do you guys like the terramore.io merch maybe i should sell it on the website
no this is just for employees for now at least module six is going to be the fastest one
getting your first client if you haven't already done it or getting your first client using this
exact formula it's going to boil down to three distinct things pick your audience
make it as specific as possible reach out right this is understanding where they are and what
they're doing a little bit right are you going through google maps checking their
um checking their photos and saying hey your profile your google profile when you when i type in
local lawyer is no good i couldn't find you and we can make that better that's a pretty specific
problem a pretty specific audience and your reach out is specific to them right um you sell a skincare
product find your audience make it even more specific and reach out right um i sell
uh skincare products okay and i want to make sure it goes directly after your uh after you wash your
face are you you see people posting that and they're using some product insert your product here
right do that one message so you at the very least learn about your customer as well as they learn about
your brand your business your product okay we're going to fly through these here warm outreach
relevance over volume find your specific niche brevity there's no way any first outreach is going to be
a long paragraph keep it specific to them whether it's a cold email or a dm and concise
right hyper specificity yep you you're getting the gist here hopefully one clear next step don't just
insert product here right in the message say reach out to me if you want more information
um are you available tuesday there's again a little like cold email lead templatey but you need to have
them take the action of what next if you're interested just say yes right make them do a next step call
out the next step we call the call to action right um copy paste these if you don't know what to say
if you're frozen in fear of talking to someone well hopefully you're not because you're running a
business here um here's the dm ones here's the email ones you should be following up quickly um
you need to understand your customer here as well you need to understand the journey of what that sales
process looks like so on your first outreach you're reaching out to 10 people do they respond same day do
they respond within 10 5 2 minutes or do they respond within two days what does that look like
how do we shrink that time frame and how do i be on top of it whether that is you're on top of your dms
you are emailing that quickly um you have a bot to do it um it's we'll get into that maybe a little
in another course we won't even talk about that now but understand your customer as well as your cadence
of responses um read the rest of this that should pertain to how often um and what to say as well
you don't necessarily have to always be cold right it doesn't have to be a cold outreach friends and
family people in your friend list of your instagram facebook snapchat whatever past co-workers people
that you know may already work in the industry reach out local owners community groups whatever you
have to do to find someone that you might have a little bit of relation to might be a little bit
more of an incentive to even respond and you'll understand response rates if you don't already
based on this exercise list them here print this out list them here uh print it out five times so you
can get 20 people on here and just start moving right and like i said you should be doing this course
as we continue you shouldn't be waiting until you're done with the course to move stop it here when
you're done doing this that's when you can move on to the next module all right
you